Ananthu K A

Pin: 628010

Kelamangalath(H) Edacochi,kochin-10 Ernakulam (Dist), Kerala. India ☐ Mobile No: +91-9995984598

E-Mail Id: ananthu.ajay92@gmail.com

Executive Synopsis

Self-motivated and goal-oriented professional with 7 + years of experience in the IT industry Expertise in mobile application development using Android and Flutter.

To pursue a challenging career in a leading and progressive research organization offering opportunities for utilizing my skills towards the growth of the organization

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

RechargeIndia Pvt Ltd, Oxford business centre, Ravipuram, Ernakulam

Senior Android Developer (From 14-10-2021 To till date)

Ewire Softtech Pvt Ltd, Kinfra Hi-Tech park, Kalamasseri Senior Software engineer (From 15-9 -2019 To 10-10-2021).

INFRAP, Infopark tbc, kaloor, Kochi

Senior Android Developer (From 25-6-2018 - To 13-9-2019).

Reference: Prasad - (Project manager: 8086766660)

Forsight Technologies, Ernakulam South, Kochi

Senior Android Developer (From 15-12-2015 - To 12-12-2017).

Projects Profile

KYC Application

Programming language :- Flutter

mPOS

Programming language :- Android, java

DDMP Merchant POS

Programming language :- Android, java

Available on Max store (custom appstore for pos terminals devices)

DDMP Sales Team application

Programming language :- Android, java

Available on Max store.

Ewire World

Programming language: - Android, java

Onepay

Programming language :- Android, java

Muthoot amzpay

Programming language: - Android, java

Ewire Rupay

Programming language :- Android, java

Link: - https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=in.MadMoveGlobal.EwireRuPay

Neericode SCB Ewire

Programming language :- Flutter

Link:- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ewire.closed_loop_flutter

Knatree

Programming language :- Android, java

Link: - https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.infrap.knatree

Invstars

Programming language :- Android, java

Link - <u>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.invstars&hl=en</u>

My Payroll Master

Programming language :- Android, java

 $Link: \underline{https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.forsight.app.mypayrollmaster\&hl=en}$

TECHNICAL COMPETENCIES

Languages/Technologies: Java, Android Firebase, Php-(yii2/ Cake), .net(c#), Kotlin, Flutter,

Other Skills: Git, Bitbucket, JIRA, AWS (deployment activities). REST Apis, Azure, Notification hub

EDUCATION

B. Tech (IT) from TocH Institute of science and technology (2013).

INTERNSHIPS

Android app development(Java) - Appzoc Solutions (10-04-2015 to 20-15-2015) ASP .NET - E Mac Solutions, Ernakulam North (14-08-203 to 24-10-2013)

PERSONAL PROFILE

Name : Ananthu K A
Date of Birth : 30/04/1992

Sex : Male
Marital Status : Married
Nationality : Indian

Father's Name : K B Ajayaghosh